makeemotion.net 2010-06-11

# Which Way To Pay - Privacy Notice

**Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 – Warnings and Disclaimers**

**As listed below:**

www.whichwaytopay.com is not authorised to give advice under the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000.

The information contained in the Material on this Site is intended for information and interest only, and not to either provide advice to, or to address the particular requirements of any individual. We do not recommend or endorse any investment, advisor or other service or product, or any material submitted by third parties, or linked to or from this Site. We do not offer any legal, financial or other advice, either regarding the nature, potential value or suitability of any particular investment, security or investment strategy, or otherwise.

You should not rely on any material in this Site to take (or refrain from taking) any decision or action. If you have any doubts you should contact an independent financial advisor.

**Information We Collect / Information Security:**

Please read the following terms and conditions carefully as these govern the use of this website. All material contained within the Compare Pre Paid website www.whichwaytopay.com is covered by a disclaimer and protected by copyright laws.

Access to this website www.whichwaytopay.com is subject to the following conditions:

We are committed to privacy and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Personal data privacy is a new and evolving area, and www.whichwaytopay.com is evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [info@whichwaytopay.com](mailto:info@whichwaytopay.com) we will assist and address any issue to the best of our abilities.

We at www.whichwaytopay.com are committed to respecting your privacy and recognise your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number). That is why we have established this privacy policy, so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. Your personal information will not be disclosed to any third party

We will use your Information to process www.whichwaytopay.com newsletters, offers and promotions. We may also use user Information for marketing purposes and to conduct research and analysis. We may provide certain your Information to others outside of www.whichwaytopay.com as permitted by law, such as to government entities or other third parties in response to subpoenas.

We will not disclose any such information outside of www.whichwaytopay.com except:

To fraud prevention agencies and other organisations who may use the information to prevent fraud and money laundering.

We may develop marketing programs and send you special offers for products and services. If you prefer not to receive offers, you may opt out by calling us on **Tel: +44 (0) 207 386 5300** or email us on [info@whichwaytopay.com](mailto:info@whichwaytopay.com). If you opt out from receiving these offers, we may still send important information about www.whichwaytopay.com or other Products and services to you.

This section explains our web security promise as you may have concerns about the security of your money over the internet or how your personal information is protected from misuse, we take every measure to protect you and your money, and here are some points to assist you on what you can do to protect yourself from online fraud.

We take every effort to secure our site and our customer's information but do not guarantee the Site will be fault free and do not accept liability for any errors or omissions that occur.
